[
  {"question": "What percentage of people sleep with a stuffed animal?", "answer": 34},
  {"question": "What percentage of adults still eat cereal for dinner?", "answer": 12},
  {"question": "What percentage of people have lied on their resume?", "answer": 56},
  {"question": "What percentage of people talk to their pets?", "answer": 85},
  {"question": "What percentage of people sing in the shower?", "answer": 63},
  {"question": "What percentage of people have re-gifted a present?", "answer": 27},
  {"question": "What percentage of people have snooped through someoneâ€™s phone?", "answer": 48},
  {"question": "What percentage of people bite their nails?", "answer": 36},
  {"question": "What percentage of people believe in aliens?", "answer": 61},
  {"question": "What percentage of people still keep their childhood toys?", "answer": 30},
  {"question": "What percentage of people talk to themselves out loud?", "answer": 70},
  {"question": "What percentage of people have gone on a blind date?", "answer": 22},
  {"question": "What percentage of people have cheated on a test?", "answer": 45},
  {"question": "What percentage of people have eaten food from the floor?", "answer": 58},
  {"question": "What percentage of people believe in ghosts?", "answer": 52},
  {"question": "What percentage of pepole exit partys without telling people they're leaving?", "answer": 25},
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have purchased condoms from gas station bathroom dispensers?",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people normally do NOT greet them using their first names??",
    "answer": 63
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people only go to the Dentist when something is wrong??",
    "answer": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have attended an Ugly Sweater Party??",
    "answer": 35
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people are more annoyed than anything else??",
    "answer": 40
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have ever had usernames (email, Twitter, etc) with the number 69 in them??",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people keep diaries or journals that they update pretty much daily??",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have purchased car washes at gas astations in the past year??",
    "answer": 43
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have parachuted out of an aircraft??",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people own more mittens than they do gloves??",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have visitied cemeteries where nobody they knew was buried??",
    "answer": 73
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have vaped??",
    "answer": 32
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people said they would keep working at their jobs if they won $900 million in the lottery??",
    "answer": 37
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have left scathing notes on strangers' cars because of poor parking jobs or other vehicular offenses??",
    "answer": 24
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people regularly talk out loud to themselves when alone??",
    "answer": 76
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of epople reguarly cut off, or avoid eating, the crusts on their sandwiches??",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people prefer brownies with nuts over nutless brownies??",
    "answer": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have donated to crowdfunding projects??",
    "answer": 70
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have photobombed total strangers??",
    "answer": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people woudl rather come up with different usernames than different passwords??",
    "answer": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people like their orange juice with pulp rather than pulp-free??",
    "answer": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people own movies starring Gerard Depardieu??",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people prefer The Rolling Stones to The Beatles??",
    "answer": 23
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have used a search engine to get information about someone before a first date??",
    "answer": 39
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have functioning VCRs in their homes??",
    "answer": 42
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people regularly pay for things costing less than a dollar with credit cards??",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people would generally rather clean the toilet than wash the dishes??",
    "answer": 32
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people wash their bed sheets at least once a week??",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people, at this very moment, have more than five magnets on their refridgerator??",
    "answer": 77
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have bought \"As Seen on TV\" or informercial products??",
    "answer": 66
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people take their Oreos apart before eating them??",
    "answer": 46
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have ever put potato chips IN a sandwich??",
    "answer": 70
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people generally ignore restaurant straws and drink straightfrom the glass??",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people would, if offered by a sexy vampire, seize the chance to become vampires themselves??",
    "answer": 45
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of people have accidentally walked in on their parents having sex??",
    "answer": 22
  }
]
